CONNOR

KING

3 High Street
Staple Hill
BS16 5HA
07496846464
Connor.king3131@gmail.com
Linkedin.com/in/connor-k
https://connor-king.github.io/



PROFILE

I am a self-motivated, enthusiastic games technology student at University of West England. I have a passion for playing and making games and love to learn! I have been coding since I was 15 years old, making mods for games and have been keen to expand and improve my skills since.



SKILLS/TRAITS

- Self-motivated
- Punctual
- Work well under pressure
- Honest employee
- Adaptable and fast learner, keen to learn and improve skills.
- Excellent problem-solving abilities
- Great numeracy abilities
- Good communication skills
- Brilliant customer service
- Advanced C++ skills, demonstrated in university through the low-level programming assignments.
- Experience of development using VR through university to make a project.
- Great **C#** skills learnt in university through using the Unity game engine.
- Advanced **Unity** skills demonstrated many times in university getting a high scoring grade by creating player controllers, basic enemy AI, camera functions and more.
- Good **Unreal Engine** skill as demonstrated on portfolio by creating an easily expandable conversation tree system.
- Good knowledge of **GML** which I used for a personal project before going to university
- Experienced user of **Git Hub**, using it to store and develop many projects.
- Moderate knowledge of Lua, developed by creating mod for the game Don't Starve.
- Good knowledge of **Photoshop**, used many times to create 2D art.



EDUCATION

Cambridge TEC Extended Diploma in ICT Level 3 (Distinction* Distinction) | Coleg Ceredigion

2014 - 2016

During this course, I learnt a lot of general ICT skills as well as some specialized skills including use of CSS, ActionScript and multiple Adobe tools.

Games Technology – BSc (Hons) | University of West England 2016 – CURRENT

This is my current course and focus right now. I have learnt many valuable skills so far including the use of C++, C#, Unity, Unreal and low-level programming. I hope to acquire a high overall grade for my course and succeed in becoming a video game programmer after my course.

EXPERIENCE

General Assistant – Bakery | Tesco

7/2016 - 9/2016 & 12/2016 - 1/2017

Main duties performed:

- Preparing and packaging baked goods
- Stocking and tidying shelves
- Overtime as a cashier

- Taking stock and calculating waste
- Cleaning the machines
- Helping customers

Door to Door Fundraiser | Home Fundraising

5/2017 - 7/2017



LANGUAGES

English | First Language

Welsh | Advanced

I was brought up in a welsh speaking secondary school and a bilingual college, I learnt to speak Welsh from a young age and learnt to speak it fluently.



INTERESTS

Gaming

Gaming has been a passion of mine since a very young age, I love to play all games, board games, card game and video games. Magic the Gathering, Rocket League and Risk are some of my favourites.

Sport

I am a very active person and playing squash, skateboarding and bike riding have kept me busy in the nice weather.

Electronics (Arduino)

Using Arduino is hobby of mine, love the idea of coding in the physical world.

Graphic Design

Graphic design is another one of my hobbies, I like to try to digital paint as well as create surreal images.



REFERENCES

Glyn Howells/Marion Phillips | Tutor – Coleg Ceredigion

Coleg Ceredigion Cardigan 01239 612032

Sarah Turner | Bakery Manager - Tesco

Tesco
Cardigan
07807 078519
cardigan@tescocafe.com